Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Mansfield, Ohio - Middletown, Ohio, 1918-1946 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Milan, Ohio - New Lexington, Ohio (Box 45, Folder 5)
- New Philadelphia, Ohio - Sandusky, Ohio (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Sidney, Ohio - Tiffin, Ohio, 1914-1939 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Toledo, Ohio, 1922-1949 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Wapakoneta, Ohio - Zanesville, Ohio, 1914-1950 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Oklahoma City, Oklahoma - Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1947-1951 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Baker City, Oregon - Portland, Oregon, 1918-1934 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1917-1948 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Altoona, Pennsylvania - Brownsville, Pennsylvania, 1938-1939 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Carbondale, Pennsylvania - Dunmore, Pennsylvania, 1934-1949 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Easton, Pennsylvania - Galeton, Pennsylvania, 1908-1935 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Harrisburg, Pennsylvania - Johnstown, Pennsylvania, 1918-1949 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Lancaster, Pennsylvania, 1914-1939 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Mahanoy City, Pennsylvania - Phillipsburg, Pennsylvania, 1918-1950 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1912-1926 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Brewery and Distr., 1931-1943 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Soft Dr., 1939-1947 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Pittston, Pennsylvania - Roscoe, Pennsylvania, 1914-1947 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Reading, Pennsylvania, 1914-1949 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Sayres, Pennsylvania - Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1915-1949 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Shamokin, Pennsylvania - Steelton, Pennsylvania, 1913-1949 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania - Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania, 1918-1949 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Williamsport, Pennsylvania - York, Pennsylvania, 1915-1948 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Providence, Rhode Island, 1914-1950 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Central City, South Dakota - Sioux Falls, South Dakota, 1913-1916 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Chattanooga, Tennessee Brewery Distr. And S.D., 1945-1950 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Chattanooga, Tennessee Brewery and Distr., 1918-1943 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Chattanooga, Tennessee Soft Drink, 1914-1945 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Memphis, Tennessee, 1931-1950 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Nashville, Tennessee, 1912-1930 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- San Antonio New Brauntels Waco - Agreement Coll., 1920-1955 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Houston Corego from Agreement File, 1918-1949 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Forth Worth Galveston Corresp. From Agreement File, 1918-1936 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Breckinridge El Paso Dallas - Corresp. From Agreement File, 1936-1950 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Breckenridge, Texas - El Paso, Texas, 1910-1946 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Forth Worth, Texas - Galveston, Texas, 1917-1941 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Houston, Texas, 1926-1946 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- San Antonio, Texas - Waco, Texas, 1918-1949 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Norfolk, Virginia (Portsmouth and Newport News) Richmond, Virginia Roanoke, Virginia, 1916-1945 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Ogden, Utah - Salt Lake City, Utah, 1918-1950 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Spokane, Washington - Walla Walla, Washington, 1911-1938 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Ellensburg, Washington - Seattle, Washington, 1915-1949 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Bluefield, Virginia - Wheeling, Virginia, 1913-1947 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Antigo, Wisconsin - Bloomer, Wisconsin, 1921-1946 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Burlington, Wisconsin - Fond Du Lac, Wisconsin, 1914-1949 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Hartford, Wisconsin - Kewaunee, Wisconsin, 1913-1950 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Fort Atkinson, Wisconsin - Green Bay, Wisconsin, 1913-1923 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- La Crosse, Wisconsin - Madison, Wisconsin, 1913-1945 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Manitowoc, Wisconsin - Merrill, Wisconsin, 1939-1950 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1911-1928 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Monroe, Wisconsin - Port Washington, Wisconsin, 1933-1945 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Potosi, Wisconsin - Theresa, Wisconsin, 1923-1945 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Two Rivers, Wisconsin - Waukesha, Wisconsin, 1909-1945 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Wausau, Wisconsin - Sheridan, Wisconsin, 1910-1944 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Calgary, Alberta, 1912-1949 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Edmonton, Alberta - Lethbridge, Alberta, 1910-1945 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Cranbrook and Fernie, British Columbia - Transcona, British Columbia, 1912-1947 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Vancouver, British Columbia - Victoria, British Columbia, 1916-1950 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Winnipeg, Manitoba, 1912-1950 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Fort Frances, Ontario - Fort Williams, Ontario, 1908-1948 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Kendra, Ontario - Tecumseh, Ontario, 1914-1950 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Toronto, Ontario, 1904-1949 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Walkersville, Ontario - Windsor, Ontario, 1912-1947 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Ville LaSalle, Quebec Montreal (Quebec City), Moose Jaw and Prince Albert, Sask. Regina, Sask. Saskatoon, Sask., 1912-1945 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Brick and Clay Workers of America, United Agreements 1944 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Brick and Clay '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Brick and Clay Workers of Amer., United, 1955-1959 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Brick and Clay Workers of Amer., United, 1960-1964 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers, 1919 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Bricklayers, Plasterers Local 39, 1900-1919 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Bricklayers, Masons, and Plasterers International Union of America - Agreements, 1945-1949 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Bricklayers, 1950-1954 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- Bricklayers, Mason and Plasterers, 1955-1959 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers, 1960-1964 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Bricklayers, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Broadcast Employees, 1950-1954 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Broadcast Employees, 1955-1959 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1960-1964 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Broadcasting Engineers, 1945-1951 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Building Service Emp. 1940-1944 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Building Service Employees International Union - Agreements, 1945-1949 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Building Service, 1950-1954 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Building Service, 1955-1959 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- Agreements, 1961-1967 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- Agreements (Misc.), 1962 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Agreements (Misc.), 1962-1966 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- Building Service Master Contract (Independent Companies), 1959 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Building Service Employees' International, 1960-1964 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Building Service Employees International Union - Agreements, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- Building Service Employees International Union, 1965-1969 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Cafeteria Employees Union, 1945 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- Canada, Communications Union, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Canada, Ontario Secondary School Teachers' Federation Agreement, 1999-2001 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Canada Union of Operating Engineers, 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Canada Policemen's Brhd of Montreal 8*56, 1968-1990 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Canada Postal Unions Council of, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- Canada Public Service Alliance, 1969-2000 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- Carpenters and Joiners of America International Union, 1910-1937 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Carpenters, 1950-1954 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Carpenters, 1955-1959 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Carpenters Joiners of Am., United Bro. of Agreements, 1941-1949 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- Carpenters and Joiners, 1940-1944 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Carpenters and Joiners, 1959-1966 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Carpenters and Joiners, 1960-1964 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Carpenters and Joiners, 1961-1964 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Carpenters and Joiners, 1959-1964 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Carpenters, 1960-1964 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Carpenters and Joiners, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Carpenters and Joiners, 1966-1972 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Carpenters and Joiners, 1965-1969 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Cement, Lime, and Gypsum Workers, 1940-1944 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Cement, 1945-1949 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Cement, 1950-1954 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Cement, 1950-1954 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Cement, Lime and Gypsum, 1955-1959 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Cement, Lime and Gypsum, 1960-1969 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Cement, 1970-1975 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Chemical, 1941-1949 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Chemical Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Chemical Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Chemical Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Chemical Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Chemical Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Chemical Workers, 1955-1969 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Chemical Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Chemical Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Chemical Workers Union, International, 1960-1964 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Chemical Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Chemical Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Cigar Makers, 1950-1954 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Civil Service Employees Assoc. Inc., 1970-1996 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- United Cloth. Hat --, 1921-1929 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Clothing and Textile Workers General, 1986-1999 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Clothing Workers, Amalgamated, 1911-1923 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Clothing Workers of Am. Amalgamated, 1924-1941 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Clothing Workers, 1945-1949 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Clothing Workers, 1950-1952 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Clothing Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- Clothing Workers, 1955-1961 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Clothing Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Clothing Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Clothing Workers, 1960-1965 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Clothing Workers of America, 1960-1964 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Clothing Workers, 1965-1969 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Clothing Workers, 1970-1975 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Communications Association American, 1940-1944 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Communications Association, 1945-1949 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Communication Association, 1950-1954 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Communicators Association, 1955-1959 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Communications Association, 1960-1964 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Communications Workers of America Agreements, 1945-1949 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Communications Workers, Am., 1955-1959 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Communications Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Communications Workers, 1953-1959 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Communication Workers, 1950-1959 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Communication Workers, 1953 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Communication Workers, 1950-1959 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Communication Workers, 1950-1954 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Communication Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Communication Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Communication Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Communication Workers, 1955-1962 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Communications Workers, 1950-1969 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Communications Workers, 1960-1965 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Communications Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Communications Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Communications Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Communications Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Communications Workers, 1960-1965 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Communications Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Communications Workers of America, 1960-1964 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Communications Workers of America, 1960-1969 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Communications Workers of America, 1966-1974 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Communications Workers of America, 1960-1969 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Communications Workers of America, 1960-1969 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Communications Workers of America, 1965-1969 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Communications Workers of America, 1974-1975 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Communications Workers of America, 1974-1975 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Communications Workers of America, 1997-2000 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Communications Workers of America, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Communications Workers of America, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Communications Workers of America, 1973-1992 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Communications Workers of America, 1974-1977 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Communications Workers of America, 1974-1978 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Communications Workers of America, 1974-1998 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Communications Workers of America, 1971-1989 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Communications Workers of America, 1971-1989 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Confederated, 1950-1954 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Cooks, Countermen, Soda Dispensers, Food Checkers, Cashiers and Assistants' Union, 1952 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Coopers, 1945-1949 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Coopers, 1950-1954 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Coopers International Union of North America Agreements, 1955-1963 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Department Store Workers of America, United, 1953-1954 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Directors Guild of America, 1960-1964 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Distillery, Rectifying and Wine Workers, 1940-1944 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Distillery, Rectifying and Wine Workers, International Union of America Agreement, 1945-1949 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Distillery, 1950-1954 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Distillery Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Distributive, Processing and Office, 1950-1954 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Distributive Workers, Inc., 1945-1949 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Communications Workers of America, 1950-1969 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Communications Workers of America, 1977-1983 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Communications Workers of America, 1974-1983 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Communications Workers of America, 1968-1983 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Communications Workers of America, 1971-1980 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Drug and Hospital Union, 1968-1970 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Education Assoc., National, 1978-1981 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Electrical Workers, I.B.E.W. 43' - 44', 1943-1944 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1944-1952 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- I.B.E.W., 1943-1944 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Electrical I.B.E.W., 1942-1946 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- I.B.E.W., 1947-1957 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Electrical I.B.E.W. '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- I.B.E.W., 1952-1956 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- I.B.E.W., 1947-1956 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- I.B.E.W., 1948-1955 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1950-1955 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1950-1955 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1953-1956 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Electrical I.B.E.W. '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1956-1961 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1955-1957 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1955 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1951-1956 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Electrical Workers, 1955-1959 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1953-1961 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- I.B.E.W., 1957-1961 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- I.B.E.W., 1957-1961 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Electrical (IBEW) Jacobs Bros Co. (Detecto Sales Inc.,), 1956 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Electrical Workers, Bro. of '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1960-1966 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1960-1965 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- I.B.E.W., 1960-1964 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, 1961-1964 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, 1960-1967 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1960-1964 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1961-1963 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) '60-'64, 1960-1964 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1964-1993 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers AFL-CIO, 1964-1967 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers AFL-CIO, 1962-1964 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Int'l Bro. Electrical Workers (IBEW) ('60-'64), 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers AFL-CIO, 1960-1967 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1961-1967 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO Local 1859, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Electrical (IBEW) Electrical Contractors of Cortland, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Electrical (IBEW), 1966 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), 1965-1969 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1964-1978 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1963-1975 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1965-1980 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1963-1969 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1965-1971 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- IBEW - '65-'69, 1965-1969 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1975-1977 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1965-1983 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, AFL-CIO, 1977-1993 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1965-1989 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1966-1980 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1971-1980 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Electrical Workers, International Board, 1972-1994 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1969-1976 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1965-1968 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1967-1969 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- IBEW 1970-, 1970-1974 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1972-1980 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 1951-1952 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, CIO, 1950-1975 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, CIO, 1953-1966 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, CIO, 1950-1960 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, CIO, 1950-1960 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, CIO, 1950-1960 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers International, 1950-1954 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Electrical IUE, 1955-1960 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Electrical IUE, 1955-1960 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- IUE-CIO, 1955-1959 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- IUERMW, AFL-CIO, 1956-1960 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 1958-1959 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers International, 1955-1959 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers International, 1955-1959 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- International Union Electrical, 1961-1967 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, 1958 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- International Union Electrical, 1958-1965 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- IUERMW, 1959-1965 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, AFL-CIO, 1960-1965 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers, 1960-1965 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Union Agreements Manual, 1962 (Box 84.1, Folder 1)
- Annotated Union Agreements, 1964 (Box 84.1, Folder 2)
- Interpretation and Application of the GE-IUE (AFL-CIO), 1962 (Box 84.1, Folder 3)
- Annotated Union Agreements, 1962 (Box 84.1, Folder 4)
- I.U.E., 1973-1974 (Box 84.1, Folder 5)
- Misc., 1938-1955 (Box 84.1, Folder 6)
- I.U.E.R.M.W., 1960-1966 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- International Union Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE), 1960-1964 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- I.U.E., 1960-1966 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- I.U.E., 1965-1970 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- I.U.E. 1965-1969 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- IUE 1970 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Electrical IUE '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- UERMW, 1950-1955 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of Am., United '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, United '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- UE 1960-1977 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers w/ Ideal Corporation Local 463 1973-1976 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- UE -1978 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine Furniture Workers, International Union of/ 1985 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Elevator Constructors '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Elevator Constructors, International Union '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Elevator Constructors 1960-1964 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Elevator Constructors, International Union of 1964-, 1964-1992 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Embroidery Workers International Union1914- (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Engineers and Architects Ass. Of Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Engineers and Architects '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Engineers, Operating 1936-1949 (Box 87, Folder 13)
- Engineers, Operating '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Engineering Employees Assoc., Seattle Professional, 1954-1975 (Box 87, Folder 15)
- Engineers, Operating '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Engineers, Operating '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Operating Engineers, 1955-1965 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Operating, Engineers, 1960-1964 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Operating, Engineers, 1964 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Engineers, Operating, 1960-1964 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Engineers, Operating 1965-1969 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Engineers Operating 1970- (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Operating Engineers AFL-CIO, 1965-1986 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Engineers, Professional 1950-1962 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Engineering Personnel, Assoc. of Scientists and Professional, 1964-1967 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Engineers, Stationery 1957-1963 (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Engineers, Architects and Draftsmen, Int' Fed. Of Technical Agreements '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Engineers, American Federation of Technical. '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Engineers, International Federation Technical '50-'54, 1950-1954 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Engineers: American Federation of Technical '55-'59, 1955-1959 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Engineers, Technical 1960-1964 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Engineers, Technical 1965-1969 (Box 89, Folder 9)
- Engineers and Scientist of California, 1960-1970 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Engineers and Scientist of Calif., 1970-1975 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Engineers and Scientists Guild, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Engraves '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Farm Equipment and Metal Workers '40-'44, 1940-1944 (Box 89, Folder 14)
- Farm Equipment '45-'49, 1945-1949 (Box 89, Folder 15)
- Farm Labor Union, National, 1949 (Box 89, Folder 16)
- Federal Employees Metal Trades Council, 1975 (Box 89, Folder 17)
- Federal Employees Metal Trades Council of Charleston w/ Charleston Naval Shipyard, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 18)
- Federal Employees, National, 1963 (Box 89, Folder 19)
- National Federation of Federal Employees, 1997 (Box 89, Folder 20)
- Firefighters 1955-1959 (Box 89, Folder 21)
- Firefighters 1950-1954 (Box 89, Folder 22)
- Firefighters, International Association of 1965-69, 1965-1969 (Box 89, Folder 23)
- International Association of Fire Fighters, 1986-1988 (Box 89, Folder 24)